#### To Whom It May Concern,

Throughout my life, I have never stopped listening to music. It is the only medium that I can consume for hours at a time. My first introduction to Run For Cover was through Daniel Bressette, the designer of Transit's *Keep This To Yourself* album art; since then Run For Cover has been a mainstay.

I started learning about Graphic Design when I was nine years old. I learned through programs like Adobe's Fireworks. Later, I taught myself the rest of the Adobe suite through means of designing whatever I could: mock album covers, internet forums signatures, etc. I am currently studying at the Maryland Institute College of Art where I entered as a Graphic Design major. When I began my Junior year I decided to change my major to Photography to broaden my horizons and round out my skills as a Graphic Designer.

After years of listening, it was when Tuesdays with Tay started that I realized that RFC was something special. I did not know that a show could mean so much to me. It meant so much to me that I built the Tuesdays with Tay Archive. This project is a perfect example as to why I am the ideal prospect for a job with RFC. I showed my dedication to the label and the people behind it before there was even a job to apply for.

As someone who has recorded their own music and currently works as a sound engineer for live bands, I understand the connection between the artist and their craft. For example, album art is beyond just a pretty picture, it is a part of the work.

Now that I am well into my Senior year, I have my eyes set on Boston as the next destination. I would love to help out in a music scene that has been a part of my life since high school. I want it to be through Run For Cover, the label that has kept me grounded for all these years.

# Noah M. Fisher

+1 (717) 645-1464 // NFISHER@MICA.EDU

#### **SKILLS**

Graphic Design (Adobe Suite [Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Premiere, After Effects]); Web Development (HTML5, CSS, JavaScript); Photography (Analog & Digital); Studio Lighting (Photo & Video); Videography; A/V & Lighting for Theatre; Professional Printing; Layout and Design for Books; 3D Modeling (Sketch Up, Blender)

#### **INTERESTS**

Meeting new people; Learning new skills, cultures, etc.; Photography & Videography; Video Games; Archiving; Seinfeld

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Freelance Graphic Designer

JAN. 2017 - PRESENT

- Music // Album design & layout commissions
- Web Development // Portfolio sites
- Documentation // Document artist's work

# **SCANNED** - Co-Founder, Art Director

Koenji, Tokyo & Baltimore, MD // AUG. 2019 - PRESENT

- Small publication based in Tokyo and Baltimore
- Limited prints of issues to feature artists from both cities.

#### OTHER EXPERIENCE

# Maryland Institute College of Art, Department of Events -

Performance Space Assistant

Baltimore, MD // OCT. 2017 - PRESENT

- Usher // Be sociable to patrons and represent MICA
- A/V Technician // Ran projection and live sound/music in the various venues across campus
- Theatre Lighting // Rigged and controlled the lights during events
- Woodworking // Built sets for student run plays

## **EDUCATION**

Maryland Institute College of Art — Photography b/w Graphic Design minor Baltimore, MD // SEPT. 2016 - PRESENT

## East Pennsboro Area High School

Enola, PA // SEPT. 2012 - MAY 2016